wsn.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy - Questions and Answers - WSN.com

## Cookie notice

You can also change you cookies configuration here

Our website uses cookies. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we put on your computer. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website, which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

How to Control Cookies

You can manage cookie usage through your browser settings. The help function in your preferred browser should provide you with the correct information. Some browsers provide helpful cookie guides:

  * Chrome: [https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647&p=cpn_cookies](https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647&p=cpn_cookies)

  * Firefox: [http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Cookies](http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Cookies)

  * Internet Explorer: [http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835](http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835)

  * Safari 5 for Mac: [http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/5.0/en/9277.html](http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/5.0/en/9277.html)

  * Opera: [http://help.opera.com/Linux/10.50/en/cookies.html](http://help.opera.com/Linux/10.50/en/cookies.html)

Alternatively, [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) provides advice on how to do this, and further information on cookies and how to manage them.

In addition Google Analytics provides its own opt-out options:

N.B. In the case of some mobile devices, it may be necessary to consult the device’s instruction manual to manage cookies effectively.

  1.     1. a.How we use Cookies

  1.     1.       1. i.The Site makes use of cookies and other technologies to assist in recording non-personal statistical information such as how much time is spent reading the content of a certain page, or which banner advertisements receive the most clicks by our users. Such technologies help us improve our Site, our marketing activities and your experience. Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Site. By using or accessing the Site, you are consenting to the Site’s use of cookies as explained further in this Clause 6.

  1.     1.       1. ii.Cookies are essentially text-only pieces of information that the Site transfers to your hard drive or other website browsing equipment for record-keeping purposes.

  1.     1.       1. iii.While information collected through cookies gives us no personal data (therefore it does not collect matters such as your name and surname) it does allow us to serve adverts and other content, which, based on the information stored by the cookie, may be of interest to you. This can include articles, customised advertisements and targeted services. Cookies therefore are used to improve your online experience, as well as for analytics and for marketing, but specifically we use Cookies on the Site for the purposes highlighted in the table at Clause 6(d) below.

  1.     1.       1. iv.Where we hold personal data about you (such as where it is provided to us during account creation) we may combine information received from cookies to your account profile.

You can disable cookies in your browser at any time, however this will reduce the value you can gain in terms of being useful and interesting content. It will also cancel any browser customisations you may have put in place. Removing cookies may also have the effect of removing your opt-out preferences from certain sites that use cookies to record opt-outs/unsubscribe preferences. 

b.sCookie Classification

Classification

| 

Description  
  
---|---  
  
Strictly necessary cookies

| 

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website.

Note. Blocking these cookies might prevent registration/authentication to the site and might make some content/functions unavailable.  
  
Performance cookies

| 

These cookies collect information about how customers use a website, for instance which pages customers go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identify a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous.  
  
Functionality cookies

| 

These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make such as your username, language or the region you are in and provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching videos or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised.   
  
Targeting/advertising cookies

| 

These cookies record your visit, the pages you have visited, the games you have played, the financial transactions you have made, and your general behaviour on the Site. These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of time you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. We will use this information to make our Site and the advertising displayed or received by you more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose who assist us in analytics.  
  
c.Cookies Behaviour

Session Cookies

Session cookies are created temporarily when a user visits the Site. Once the user leaves the Site/closes the browser, the session cookie is deleted.

Persistent Cookies

A persistent cookie file remains on the user’s device and is re-activated when the user visits the Site that created that particular cookie. These cookies expire after a certain period (set in the file), or can be removed manually.

  1. d.Cookies Used

Cookie Name

| 

Expiration Date

| 

Third Party?

| 

Reason for Use

| 

Classification  
  
---|---|---|---|---  
  
_ga

| 

2 years

| 

YES

| 

Used to distinguish users (Google Analytics)

| 

Performance  
  
_gat

| 

1 minute

| 

YES

| 

Used to throttle request rate (Google Analytics)

| 

Performance  
  
_gid

| 

1 day

| 

YES

| 

Used to distinguish users (Google Analytics)

| 

Performance  
  
akavpau_ppsd

| 

session based

| 

YES

| 

Used to allow transactions from Paypal on the online shop (if available)

| 

Functionality  
  
AKDC

| 

30 minutes

| 

YES

| 

Used to allow transactions from Paypal on the online shop (if available)

| 

Functionality  
  
fr

| 

1 Minute

| 

YES

| 

Used by Facebook for advertising purposes

| 

Tracking  
  
has_js

| 

session_based

| 

NO

| 

Used to save if JavaScript is enabled in the browser

| 

Functionality  
  
NID

| 

6 months

| 

YES

| 

Used by Google Tag Manager to run scripts

| 

Functionality  
  
optimizelyBuckets

| 

10 years

| 

YES

| 

Used for A/B testing and optimization of marketing campains

| 

Performance  
  
optimizelyEndUserId

| 

10 years

| 

YES

| 

Used for A/B testing and optimization of marketing campains

| 

Performance  
  
optimizelyPendingLogEvents

| 

1 day

| 

YES

| 

Used for A/B testing and optimization of marketing campains

| 

Performance  
  
optimizelySegments

| 

10 years

| 

YES

| 

Used for A/B testing and optimization of marketing campains

| 

Performance  
  
PHPSESSID

| 

session based

| 

NO

| 

Used to track user session internally

| 

Session  
  
pll_language

| 

1 day

| 

NO

| 

Used to track user language

| 

Functionality  
  
sc.ASP.NET_SESSIONID

| 

session based

| 

YES

| 

Used for checking and optimizing user interaction with the page

| 

Performance  
  
session

| 

1 day

| 

NO

| 

Used to track user session internally

| 

Session  
  
## PRIVACY POLICY

At  WSN.com we value your privacy as much as you do and we have created this Privacy Policy that ensures your peace of mind. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”), together with the General Terms and Conditions of the Site, sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting our Site you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

  1. 1\. DATA PROTECTION

  1. a.Personal data, or personal information, means any information about a person from which that person can be identified (“Personal Data”). It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data).

  2. b. You may contact the data controller for any questions in relation to the manner in which we use your Personal Data at dataprotection@gig.com.

#### 2. WHAT AND HOW PERSONAL INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

We will collect and process data about you depending under which of the following category/ies you belong: 

  1. a.Browsing through the Site

With regard to each of your visits to our Site, whether you have a User Account (as defined below) or not, we might automatically collect the following information:

  * Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, your internet service provider (ISP), your device, your location, your operating system and platform and other online identifiers. While this information is non-personal, we do treat it with the same level of security and afford it the protection we afford to your Personal Data. It is only used for internal analysis of user trends, so that we can best optimise the Site to offer a superior online experience.

  * If you use our Site on your mobile device, we may collect your mobile carrier information and the unique device id number.

  * Information about your visit to the Site, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) and page interaction information.

  * Information received from cookies. 

  * The Site also uses certain analytics tools that enables the Site to collect data from analytics platforms. The Site uses both its own analytics tools as well as third party analytics providers. Information collected through data analytics includes information on the Operating System (OS) running on your device, Internet Protocol (IP) address (which may be used to obtain your geolocation), access times, browser type, and language, and the website you visited before our Sites. Please refer to Clause 6 (Cookies) of this Privacy Policy for further details on analytics providers we use.

  1. b.Opting to receive our Newsletter or Opting into any promotion

When you choose to join our email newsletter or opt into any promotion, we will also record your name and email address and we will contact you via email.

You may opt out of receiving newsletter and promotional emails from the Site by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your Account.

  1. c. Creating a User Account

  1. i.When you create a free online user account on the Site (“User Account”), apart from the information referred in Clause 2(a) above, we will also record the following information about you: name, date of birth, email address and username.______________________.

  2. ii.If you choose to ‘Register with Facebook’, the information you choose to share with us may include the basic information available in your Facebook profile (including your email address, status updates and a list of your contacts). We will only receive registration information from Facebook and no other information. Facebook will be able to tell you more about how they use and process your data whenever you connect with us through them.

  1. d.Contacting us

When you contact our support team for assistance with regards to any information on the Site we may also record all the information you provide to us.

#### 3\. HOW YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IS USED

  1. a.Your personal information is used by the Site to:

  1.     1.       1. i.Deliver Marketing Communications - to keep you up to date with new information, announcements, relevant updates and other events deemed to be of value to you. You will receive any such information through email and other forms of electronic communications only if you have opted to receive any such information prior to signing up, or through modifying your settings in your User Account to allow for receipt of such information. You may choose at any time to opt out of receiving communication by accessing your User Account and modifying the settings or by following the relevant unsubscribe link.

  1.     1.       1. ii.When you enter any competitions, giveaways or sweepstakes offered by the Site we will use your personal information to administer such programs. 

  1. b.We will also use your personal information to verify your account information should the need to verify such information arises.

  1. c.Personalisation and Interest-based advertising - The Site runs targeted advertisements based on your personal information. This means that the Site provides you with advertisements specifically based on your interests that we would have recorded through your interactions with the Site or else through information collected by analytics platforms that we use or through cookies. For more information on data analytics used to run these targeted advertisements and how you can opt out of them please see Clause 6 (d) of this Privacy Policy. 

4\. CATEGORIES OF DATA HELD ABOUT YOU

The personal data collected and processed on you can be grouped into the following categories:

  * Identity Data includes first name, maiden name, last name, username or similar identifier, marital status, title, date of birth, gender, employment status and occupation.

  * Contact Data includes residential address, email address and telephone numbers.

  * Technical Data includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.

  * Profile Data includes your username and password (encrypted), login and logout times.

  * Usage Data includes information about how you use the Site.

  * Marketing and Communications Data includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.

5\. LAWFUL BASIS FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL DATA

We have set out below, in a table format, a description of all the ways we plan to use your personal data, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate.

Purpose/Activity

| 

Category of data

| 

Lawful basis for processing including basis of legitimate interest  
  
---|---|---  
  
To register you as a new user

| 

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(c) Profile Data

| 

  1. (a)Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated)

To manage our relationship with you which will include:

(a) Notifying you about changes to our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy

(b) Maintain a User Account with us.

| 

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(c) Profile

(d)Marketing and Communications

| 

(a) Performance of a contract with you

(c) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated)  
  
To send you promotional information and newsletters

| 

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(c) Profile

(d) Usage

(e)Marketing and Communications

| 

  1. (a)Consent (if we contact you by means of direct marketing.

To administer and protect our business and the Site (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data)

| 

Technical

| 

(a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise)  
  
To deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you

| 

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(c) Profile

(d) Usage

(e) Marketing and Communications

(f) Technical

| 

Necessary for our legitimate interests (to deliver relevant interests to you through the Site based on your past activity and preferences)  
  
To use data analytics to improve our website, products, marketing, customer relationships and experiences

| 

(a) Technical

(b) Usage

| 

Necessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of users, to keep our Site updated and relevant and to develop our business)  
  
To make suggestions and recommendations to you about products that may be of interest to you

| 

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(c) Technical

(d) Usage

(e) Profile

(f) Marketing and Communications Data

| 

  1. (a)Necessary for our legitimate interests (to grow our business) if suggestions are delivered via the Site.

  1. (b)Consent (if we contact you by means of direct marketing).

#### 6\. COOKIES & ANALYTICS

Cookies

Our website uses cookies. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we put on your computer. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website, which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

For more information on Cookies, please see our Cookie Notice.

Analytics

The site also uses Analytics.

Whether you have a User Account or not, we may use Google Analytics and Matomo Analytics, as well as any other analytics providers that we may use from time to time, to advertise on the Site and/or on third-party Sites to you after you visit our Site. We and third-parties like Google and Matomo, use first party cookies and third party cookies to inform, optimise and serve ads based on your past visits to our Site:

  1.     1.       1. i.Google Analytics

  1. 1.Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Site. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. 

  2. 2.We use Google Analytics’ 3rd-party audience data such as age, gender and interests to understand the behaviour of our customers. We also work with companies that collect information about your online activities to provide advertising targeted to suit your interests and preferences. This means that you may from time to time see several advertisements on the Site or other sites you browse because we contract with Google and other companies to target our advertisements based on data we or they have collected, including data collected through cookies. These companies may also be able to collect information when you click on advertisements on the Site, which helps track and manage the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. 

  3. 3.You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page ([https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated)). Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for your browser ([https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)). Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

  1.     1.       1. 

#### 7\. PERSONAL INFORMATION DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES

  1. a.The Site does not trade, share, transfer or disclose any of your personal information, except as is otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by and in accordance with applicable law.

  1. b.We do seek to partner with companies who provide services, solutions and promotions we feel will be of value to our customers, and in such instances we will provide you with any such services, solutions and promotions of such other companies. . 

  1. c.The Site also reserves the right to provide statistics about your use of the Site, sales, traffic, and other statistical information relating to the Site to third parties, without however, identifying your identity.

  1. d.The Site may provide your personal data to its affiliates or related companies for legitimate business purposes.

  1. e.In the event of a merger, reorganisation or sale of the Site we may transfer all recorded personal and non-personal information to all relevant third parties. In this case, the Site will inform users before personal information becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

  1. f.We may release your information should we be required to do so by law in order to comply with any legal processes. 

  1. g.We do not provide any warranty against the use of your information by third party sites linked to, and from, the Site.

#### 8\. YOUR RIGHTS

Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data:

  1. a.Request access to your personal data. You have the right to access information held about you. We shall comply with any reasonable access request. In the events that the access request involves a disproportionate amount of work, we reserve the right, in line with applicable law, to charge a fee covering the work involved.

  2. b.Request correction of your personal data. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.

  3. c.Request erasure of your personal data. You have the right to ask us to delete any information we hold about you which is not relevant to purpose for which we collect it. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You may also request for us to delete all your personal data, in which case we ask you to close your account. There may be legal obligations which may prohibit us from deleting all or any information held about you immediately at the time of the request (such as Anti-Money Laundering legislation), however we will process your request at the earliest opportunity whenever any applicable data retention period expires.

  4. d.Object to processing of your personal data. You have a right to object to our processing of personal data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground as you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes, in which case we ask you to untick the relevant tick-box for direct marketing, prior to creating a User Account, or to modify the settings of your User Account, which grants us the consent to process your data for marketing communications. In some cases, we may demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your information which override your rights and freedoms.

  5. e.Request restriction of processing your personal data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your personal data in the following scenarios: (a) if you want us to establish the data’s accuracy; (b) where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it; (c) where you need us to hold the data even if we no longer require it as you need it to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or (d) you have objected to our use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.

  6. f.Request transfer of your personal data (data portability request). This enables you to request your personal data. We will provide to you, your personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.

  7. g.Right to withdraw consent for direct marketing. You have the right at any time to change your mind in relation to us being able to contact you with direct marketing. You can exercise your right to stop receiving direct marketing by accessing your account and unticking the consent boxes related to direct marketing or by contacting customer support. Any withdrawal of consent for the processing of personal data for marketing purposes will apply for the Site only. 

  8. h.We will retain copies of any communications that you send to us (including copies of any emails) in order to maintain accurate records of the information that we have received from you.

  9. i.You can also exercise your rights at any time by contacting us at dataprotection@gig.com. 

#### 9\. PROTECTION OF CHILDREN

  1. a.The Site is an online gambling information portal and as such none of its marketing content, products, services or promotions are appropriate for, or targeted at, children and visitors under the age of 18 years of age (or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction).

  1. b.The Site does not knowingly solicit or collect personal data from children below the age of 18. If the Site discovers that it has accidentally collected personal data from a child below 18, it will remove that child’s personal data from its records as soon as reasonably possible. 

  1. c.The Site bears no responsibility for the actions taken by children or visitors under the age of 18 (or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction) based on the content found on the Site, or any of its sub-domains and pages, nor our outbound marketing campaigns (including but not limited to our email newsletter).

#### 10\. GENERAL ACCOUNT REGISTRATION POLICY

  1.     1. a.You can register a free account with the Site. Please note it is not obligatory to do so in order to continue using the Site and participating in the promotions on offer, unless stated otherwise.

  1.     1. b.Account registration is not available to children and visitors under the age of 18 years of age (or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction). In accordance with this Privacy Policy the Site does not knowingly record, store or disclose any personal information related to children and visitors under the age of 18 years of age (or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction).

  1.     1. c.Once you have registered an account you can at any time request for the account to be de-activated, or deleted. Please note we will retain the registered information in our secure archive for statistical and analysis purposes, as explained better in Clause 11 below (Data Retention).

#### 11\. DATA RETENTION

  1. a.You can ask us to delete your data by closing your User Account. In that case, we will immediately delete all information aside from that which we may from time to time be required to retain by law. 

  1. b.In some circumstances we may anonymise your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

#### 12\. CUSTOMER ACCOUNT CONFIDENTIALITY

  1. a.Your personal information will only be exposed to staff members of the Site who require access to certain data in order to perform the functions associated with their position in the company.

  1. b.Your personal information is password protected in a secure digital encryption environment. 

  1. c.We abide by all regulations for the protection of personal information.

#### 13\. GENERAL DATA SECURITY

The Site has implemented the necessary and digital and infrastructure security measures at the physical IT and data storage facilities to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your information.

#### 14\. CONTENT CONDITIONS

  1. a.Due to the realities of maintaining the Site and other digital content we cannot guarantee that all content will be accurate at all times.

  2. b.For this and other reason the Site reserves the right to adjust and make amendments to the information contained within the Site without notice.

  3. c.It is worth noting that some services and promotions are subject to regulatory and jurisdictional restrictions, and are therefore not available in all markets.

The responsibility lies with you to ensure that any information you respond to is currently valid before committing to the required action.

#### 15\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy. In the event that you do not agree with any changes, we recommend that you contact customer support or otherwise close your account. 

#### 16. OTHER SITES

#### As soon as you leave the Site or are otherwise redirected to another site (“Third Party Site”) by, for instance, clicking on an advertisement or a banner of third party brands advertised on the Site, the terms and conditions, the private policies and data processing practices (and which we have no control over) of the Third Party Site shall apply, and the terms and conditions of the Site and this Privacy Policy shall no longer apply to you and to any use you make on any such Third Party Site.
